<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="D4F9139E-A2E5-48A8-9E1B-35115315B142">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20131030" date="2013-10-30 14:50:27 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Diaries of a teenaged second&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="29__Guest_Post_by_Brandon_McDonald__files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="420px" height="183px"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>*Guest Post by Brandon McDonald*</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Saturday, November 29, 2008</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>I hate most things.&#xD;&#xD;First off, it is my job to set the table - our coach told me so - metaphorically speaking of course. Without those first two rocks, we wouldn&#x2019;t be where we are now. I am kind of a big deal. Much like now, and with me setting the table, I will commence with this post. &#xD;&#xD;I don&#x2019;t really like these guys. They are clowns. Mike, ha, he wears shirts that are too small. Ed; he&#x2019;s like a sheep dog. He needs to cut his hair. (and I&#x2019;m not saying that because I cut my hair short, fyi I&#x2019;m not balding, it&#x2019;s just short) And Andrew, what could I say that hasn&#x2019;t already been said. He thinks that we&#x2019;re friends, I am reluctant to tell him otherwise. &#xD;&#xD;I try to be a sheltered person in the curling world, this is completely opposite to my university life. I go to clubs, I dance, I&#x2019;m a fan of Kanye and the like. Futhermore I rock my Band of Brothers jeans, wicked Air Force Ones and clutch rock&amp;republic shirts. Unknown to the guys I roll in a souped up Jag. I like to spin up and down Bankside, O&#x2019;Connor and Wellington in Ohh&#x2019;town....and I don&#x2019;t call it that cause the ladies love my moves......but it adds to the ambiance. &#xD;&#xD;Cutlery. Check. Napkins. Yup. Salt n Pepper. You know it!&#xD;Now that we have the preliminaries out of the way. The rest of the team may proceed. &#xD;&#xD;Peace out. &#xD;B Wheels McD. &#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
