<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog</link>
    <description>Throughout the season, second Mike Flemming will be writing blog posts.  Our goals are to keep you informed of our progress, and entertained by it.

This blog will be the best way to keep track of Team Flemming as we blaze a trail of glory across the province.</description>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Regional Wrap Up</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog/Entries/2008/12/1_Quick_Regional_Wrap_Up.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18f53596-d72f-40d4-8763-2a86d0a1957e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 1 Dec 2008 09:07:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>Saturday: check.  &#x2028;A side final vs our boy Terry on Sunday.  After Lil Wayne got me Jacked and brandon did his lame girly stretching we took the ice ready for battle.  Hey, sometimes the bad guy wins.. look at the Lion King when Mufassa dies!&lt;br/&gt;&#x2028;So the B final was another epic battle circa 1979-- pre free guard zone.  It was a battle of who was going to blink first. Luckily Will-T-Lettuce glued our eyelids open. Eight blanks and a final score of 2-1 showed everyone why curling doesn&#x2019;t have very much fan support. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Also shout out to Hodgson rockin B-side. They will own the girls side in Ganknock.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Weather left us stuck in Collingwood so we munched all you can eat chicken wings and crashed at Casa Nash again.  Another Huge thanks to them for their hospitality.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;God of War&#x2028;May your Hammer be mighty.&lt;br/&gt;Flemm</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object050.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog/Entries/2008/12/1_Quick_Regional_Wrap_Up.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>*Guest Post by Brandon McDonald*</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog/Entries/2008/11/29__Guest_Post_by_Brandon_McDonald_.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48bff80b-b220-4919-906e-ca5fb0b1b014</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 20:23:32 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>I hate most things.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;First off, it is my job to set the table - our coach told me so - metaphorically speaking of course. Without those first two rocks, we wouldn&#x2019;t be where we are now. I am kind of a big deal. Much like now, and with me setting the table, I will commence with this post. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I don&#x2019;t really like these guys. They are clowns. Mike, ha, he wears shirts that are too small. Ed; he&#x2019;s like a sheep dog. He needs to cut his hair. (and I&#x2019;m not saying that because I cut my hair short, fyi I&#x2019;m not balding, it&#x2019;s just short) And Andrew, what could I say that hasn&#x2019;t already been said. He thinks that we&#x2019;re friends, I am reluctant to tell him otherwise. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I try to be a sheltered person in the curling world, this is completely opposite to my university life. I go to clubs, I dance, I&#x2019;m a fan of Kanye and the like. Futhermore I rock my Band of Brothers jeans, wicked Air Force Ones and clutch rock&amp;amp;republic shirts. Unknown to the guys I roll in a souped up Jag. I like to spin up and down Bankside, O&#x2019;Connor and Wellington in Ohh&#x2019;town....and I don&#x2019;t call it that cause the ladies love my moves......but it adds to the ambiance. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Cutlery. Check. Napkins. Yup. Salt n Pepper. You know it!&lt;br/&gt;Now that we have the preliminaries out of the way. The rest of the team may proceed. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Peace out. &lt;br/&gt;B Wheels McD. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object051.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog/Entries/2008/11/29__Guest_Post_by_Brandon_McDonald_.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regional Game Uno</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog/Entries/2008/11/29_Regional_Game_Uno.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c990e50c-8c98-4698-9341-b1e6b142c876</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 12:20:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>Word from Collingwood again. Arrived in Meaford this morning bright and early for game #1. After changing in the closet Meaford had set up for us, Will started getting on my nerves and I decided to show him who&#x2019;s boss. We had a serious UFC battle royale. It would have been a good fight if Wilload-of-crap hadn&#x2019;t cheated. I won&#x2019;t go into the details but I think everyone knows who the real winner was. (editor&#x2019;s note: Will always wins, he has &#x201C;The Belt&#x201D;)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So the game was just like Kirsten Dunst - beautiful and nice to look at.   Our next game is at 5 so we&#x2019;re preparing mentally.  Serious pingpong minus a net, and munchin on cheerios.  I love chez Nash.  Who else has a urinal IN their house! That&#x2019;s when you know you&#x2019;ve made it.&lt;br/&gt;&#x2028;I&#x2019;m out to go birdwatching around town. Starting at the slopes, then I&#x2019;ll go from there... &lt;br/&gt;peace &#x2028;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object056.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog/Entries/2008/11/29_Regional_Game_Uno.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trip to Meaford</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog/Entries/2008/11/28_The_Trip_to_Meaford.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7d0ec15-27e5-4a2f-9ef7-c0619f0d045f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 22:18:13 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>Hello Jacks and Jills, Harrys and Sallys,&#x2028;&#x2028;Reporting to you live from Collingwood Ontario.  We just arrived at my boy T-Nash&#x2019;s house and are chillin in his dope basement. We&#x2019;ve got PS3 pingpong and enough beds for Ed&#x2019;s entire anthropology class.  Big shout out to the Nash famjam who is putting us up. &#x2028;&#x2028;Dinner was hey badaboombadabing at Mario&#x2019;s residence.  We munched on about twelve loaves of bread and were pleasantly surprised to find their TV tuned to Best Damn Sports Show Hooters Pageant!  This was quite the dinner distraction for all of us (less Brandominatrix).  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Tomorrow is the big first day of Regionals and Willbot is telling us to go to bed now. &lt;br/&gt;To our only fan and my Number one boss T$, keep your lifejacket on and relax-- and thanks in advance for the words of wisdom.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Stay Ripe&lt;br/&gt;Flemm</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object053.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog/Entries/2008/11/28_The_Trip_to_Meaford.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Zoned in and Eat</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog/Entries/2008/11/25_Get_Zoned_in_and_Eat.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97752a8b-77fc-4490-96cb-840e0f048aef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 21:59:51 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>I haven&#x2019;t blogged in a while so I should catch everyone up.&#xA0; The Oktoberfest Spiel was Wunderbar! The munch-for-lunch was excellent, Ein Prosit. &#xA0;Then on to a Halloween KW-spiel. &#xA0;We played like we had seen a ghost. And As for the halloween party, the costumes were... revealing... and regrettable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We have been practicing early in the morning (6:30AM, and Will's dumb idea). But it seems to have paid off because this past weekend at zones we played like we were getting paid. Unfortunately we weren't.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Brandonia shot like a real cowgirl, Ed Circus-yr was playing smooth like a shaved cat and Andypandy was dropping shots like he was being whipped at home. The real hero was Coach Willdom. He Found time in his busy schedule to boost us with Boost. &#xA0;Plus he and I had an epic wrestling match pre-zones to get jacked. I wont say who won but I think it was a pretty even match... Judges decision.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Im out &#xA0;to try and work off our zone-victory-feast, (nachos, spring-rolls, chicken wings, steak, french fries, French bread). Top it off with a nap and it made for a hell of a day.&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;word Meaford.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object046.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog/Entries/2008/11/25_Get_Zoned_in_and_Eat.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, MMMM d, y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>file://localhost/Users/andrewflemming/Sites/teamflemming/Blog</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>5</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
