<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Andrew</title><link>https://blog.andrewflemming.net/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Andrew</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Andrew Flemming</copyright><atom:link href="https://blog.andrewflemming.net/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Check</title><link>https://blog.andrewflemming.net/projects/check/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.andrewflemming.net/projects/check/</guid><description>I created Check in the summer of 2011, and maintained it until its retirement in 2019.
Check was an iPad and iPhone list manager that was as simple as it was beautiful. Set in Futura, on simulated stacks of paper, even the most mundane lists came to life as works of art. Finally, your lists could be beautiful.
Check would sync your lists between your devices using Apple&amp;rsquo;s iCloud service. So wherever you are, you could have your shopping lists, to-do lists, bucket lists, or whatever other list you could think of.</description></item><item><title>CurlBook</title><link>https://blog.andrewflemming.net/projects/curlbook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.andrewflemming.net/projects/curlbook/</guid><description>From its release in 2009 to its retirement in 2018 CurlBook was the premier curling coaching software for iOS, used around the world by national teams, including Curling Canada.
Learn more about CurlBook at it&amp;rsquo;s archived website</description></item><item><title>Festivus Grievances</title><link>https://blog.andrewflemming.net/projects/grievances/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.andrewflemming.net/projects/grievances/</guid><description>A silly app for iOS, iPadOS, and watchOS used to keep track of all the ways you&amp;rsquo;ve been disappointed by the people in your life. You enter grievances all year, and they remain hidden from everyone - even yourself. Keep all that anger bottled up until Festivus dinner and the airing of the grievances!
Download from the App Store</description></item><item><title>SmartBroom</title><link>https://blog.andrewflemming.net/projects/smartbroom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.andrewflemming.net/projects/smartbroom/</guid><description>The SmartBroom — developed and sold by my company Canadian Curling Tools Ltd. — is a powerful tool for curlers interested in improving the effectiveness of their sweeping. It is used by national organizations and curling clubs around the world.
Learn more</description></item></channel></rss>